# ANJUSHA THEKKUMKATTIL SHAJU



## CONTACT

anjusha1994@gmail.com

Clausthal-Zellerfeld, Germany - 38678

in Anjusha T.S

#### **SKILLS**

Languages

Malayalam

**English** 

German

## Technical Skills HTML/CSS **JavaScript** Angular 6 **React JS React Native PHP-Laravel** Node Js **Python Firebase MySQL DynamoDB PostgreSQL** MongoDB GraphQL **AWS Services** GIT **GitHub Bitbucket Docker Unit Testing** ОКТА LaTeX C++ **Operating Systems** Linux macOS Windows

#### **SUMMARY**

Accomplished software developer with 4 years of work experience with excellent computer programming skills. Well-aware of all technical happenings and making sure to deal with any issues in a timely manner. Experience in website construction, by designing with creative ideas and innovative plans to attract potential customers.

# **WORK HISTORY**

m 05/2021 - present

Working Student Software Developer

Funanga AG Berlin, Germany

- · Writing and implementing efficient code
- Fixing and improving existing software
- Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications.

**1** 01/2018 - 10/2020

**♀** Zeefasys Pvt.ltd India

Full stack developer

- Developing and implementing the front-end and back-end portions of an application.
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use
- · Identified and suggested new technologies and tools for enhancing product value and increasing team productivity.

**6** 08/2016 - 01/2018

**Bpract Software Solutions Pvt.ltd** 

Software Developer

- Optimize applications for maximum speed and scalability.
- · Collaborate with teams and stakeholders
- Developed new user-facing features.
- Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software
- · Ensuring user experience determines design choices

#### **EDUCATION**

10/2020 - Present

Technische Universität Clausthal. Germany

Master's in Informatik

**6** 07/2012 - 04/2016

Anna University, India

**Bachelor of Engineering** 

• Electronics and communication CGPA: 7.46.

## **EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE**

- Participated in the "4th National Conference on Communication, Electrical and Electronics System".
- Published My Project Paper in "International Journal of Research in Electronics (IJERT)".